A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1972-2012
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence, subject files, and board meeting records (Accession 44640), 1977-1990 (bulk 1987-1990)., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes).
  - Administrative Services: New Building Site, 1989 July-Dec (Box 5)
  - Administrative Services: New Building Site - Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Administrative Services: Risk Management, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Administrative Services: Human Resources, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services: Human Resources - Employee Assistance Program, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services: Social Committee, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services: Management Information Systems, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services: Management Information Systems - Steering Committee, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services: Public Relations, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services: Annual Report, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services: Balance Sheet / Newsletter, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services: Support Services, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services: Body Shop, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services: Employee Cafeteria Advisory Committee, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Executive: Articles of interest, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Executive: Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Executive: Commissioners, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Executive: Board Retreat, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Executive: Meetings, speaking engagements, etc., 1990 (Box 6)
  - Executive: Meetings, speaking engagements, etc. - Nelson County Water Project, 1989 Nov (Box 6)
  - Executive: Meetings, speaking engagements, etc. - Fannie Mae Housing Conference, 1990 Apr (Box 6)
  - Executive: Meetings, speaking engagements, etc. - Board meeting, 1989 Dec (Box 6)
  - Executive: Internal Auditor, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Executive: Audit and Management Letters, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Executive: United Way Campaign, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Executive: United Way Campaign, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Executive: American Security Bank, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Executive: Non-Profit Housing Groups, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Executive: Real Estate Advisory Board, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Executive: Tobacco Row, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Executive: Virginia Executive Institute, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Fund, 1989 Sept-Dec (Box 7)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Fund - Brookland Park, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Fund - Hampton Emergency Shelter, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Finance: Director, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Finance: BMIR Loans, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Executive Director: Secretary of Administration, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Executive Director: Secretary of Economic Development, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Executive Director: Secretary of Economic Development, 1989 Oct-Dec (Box 7)
  - Executive Director: Secretary of Economic Development, 1990 Jan-June (Box 7)
  - Executive Director: Agency Head meetings, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Executive Director: Danville Textile Plant, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Executive Director: Media alerts, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Executive Director: Rural Economic Development Conference, 1990 June-July (Box 7)
  - Executive Director: Rural Economic Development Conference, 1990 Aug-Sept (Box 7)
  - Executive Director: Rural Economic Development Conference, 1990 Aug-Dec (Box 7)
  - Executive Director: Rural Economic Development, 1990 (Box 7)
- Correspondence, subject files, and board meeting records (Accessions 44847, 45144, 45238, 45268, 51901 51962), 1972-2010., Extent: 37 cu. ft. (37 boxes).
  Alphabetical
  - Administration, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 7)
  - Administration, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 6)
  - Administration, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 6)
  - Administration, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)
  - Administration, Secretary of: State Training Advisory Committee (Acc. 45268), 1993-1994 (Box 5)
  - Administrative Services Division: Architectural services for lobby (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Body Shop (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Budget (Acc. 44847), 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Budget (Acc. 44847), 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Budget (Acc. 45238), 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Budget (Acc. 45268), 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Cafeteria Advisory Committee (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Communications (Acc. 45144), undated (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Computer News (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1991 July-December and 1992 January-June (Box 1)
  - Administative Services Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Director of Administrative Services position (Acc. 45144), 1991 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Good News (Acc. 45144), 1983-1989 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Human Resources (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Human Resources (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Human Resources (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Human Resources - Classification Committee(Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Human Resources - Classification and Pay Study (Acc. 45268), 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Human Resources - Kelly Temporary Services (Acc. 45238), 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Information Technology (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Legal aspects of supervision (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: MAI Study issues (Acc. 45144), 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Management Information Systems (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Management Information Systems (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Management Information Systems - Computer News (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Management Information Systems Steering Committee (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Management Information Systems Study (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Management Information Systems Study (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Meetings held at Virginia Housing Development Authority (Acc. 45144), 1992 January-December (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Meetings held at Virginia Housing Development Authority (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Meetings held at Virginia Housing Development Authority (Acc. 45238), 1993 July-December (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Meeting held at Virginia Housing Development Authority (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: New building general corresponence (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: New building meetings (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Nonprofit Affiars (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: OSDAM (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Public Relations (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Public Relations (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Public Relations - Annual report (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Social Committee (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Social Committee (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Social Committee (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Social Committee (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Support Services (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Support Services (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Support Services (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services Division: Support Services (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services Division: Virginia Business articles (Acc. 44847), 1988-1989 (Box 3)
  - Agency Head Retreat (Acc. 44847), 1990 November (Box 8)
  - Agency Head Retreat (Acc. 45238), 1992 March (Box 6)
  - Agency Head Retreat (Acc. 51901), 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Attorney General (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Attorney General (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Attorney General - meeting (Acc. 45144), 1992 Feb (Box 3)
  - Attorney General (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Attorney General (Acc. 51901), 2009 (Box 2)
  - Audit and Management letters (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 5)
  - Audit correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1984 (Box 1)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts (Acc. 45238), 1985 (Box 1)
  - Bills: HJR 287 (Acc. 45238), 1987 (Box 1)
  - Board for People with Disabilities (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Board for Rights of the Disabled (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 2)
  - Board of Conflict of Interest and Code of Conduct (Acc. 44847), 1988 (Box 4)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1975 July 15 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1975Aug 19 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1975 Sept 16 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1975 Oct 21 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1975 Nov 18 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1975 Dec 16 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1976 Jan 20 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1976 Feb 17 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1976 Mar 16 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1976 Apr 20 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1976 Apr 20 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1976 May 18 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1976 June 15 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1976 July 20 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1976 Aug 17 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1976 Sept 21 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1976 Oct 19 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1976 Nov 16 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1976 Dec 21 (Box 6)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1978 Jan 17 (Box 4)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1978 Feb 21 (Box 4)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1978 Mar 21 (Box 4)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1978 Apr 18 (Box 4)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1978 May 16 (Box 4)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1978 June 20 17 (Box 4)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1978 July 18 (Box 4)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1978 Aug 24 (Box 4)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1978 Sep 19 (Box 4)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1978 Oct 17 (Box 4)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1978 Nov 21 (Box 4)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1978 Dec 19 (Box 4)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Jan 16 (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Feb 20 (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Mar 20 (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Apr 17 (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Apr 16 (Box 1)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 May 15 (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 June 16 (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 July 16 (Box 1)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Jan 17 (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Aug 20 (Box 1)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Aug 21 (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Sept 17 (Box 1)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Sep 18 (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Oct 18 (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Nov 19 (Box 1)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Nov 20 (Box 3)
  - Board Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1979 Dec 18 (Box 3)
  - Board meeting (Acc. 45238), 1984 December (Box 1)
  - Board meeting (Acc. 45238), 1988 December (Box 1)
  - Board meeting - Building Committee (Acc. 45238), 1988 December (Box 1)
  - Board meeting - Fund Committee (Acc. 45238), 1988 December (Box 1)
  - Board meeting - Fund Committee (Acc. 45238), 1989 January (Box 1)
  - Board Retreat(Acc. 45144), 1991 (Box 3)
  - Board Retreat(Acc. 45268), 1993 April (Box 2)
  - Board Retreat (Acc. 45268), 1993 May (Box 2)
  - Board Retreat (Acc. 45268), 1993 November (Box 2)
  - Board Retreat (Acc. 51901), 2009 (Box 1)
  - Bond Allocation (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 5)
  - Bond Allocation (Acc. 45144), 1990 (Box 3)
  - Bond Allocation (Acc. 45268), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Bond Allocation (Acc. 51901), 2009 (Box 1)
  - Bond Allocation (Acc. 51962), 2010 (Box 1)
  - Budget (Acc. 45238), 1977 (Box 2)
  - Budget (Acc. 45238), 1978 (Box 2)
  - Budget (Acc. 45238), 1979 (Box 2)
  - Budget (Acc. 45238), 1980 (Box 2)
  - Budget (Acc. 45238), 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - Chesterfield Proffers (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 5)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-February (Box 5)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 March-April (Box 5)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 May-June (Box 5)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-Mar (Box 1)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 51901), 2009 Apr-June (Box 1)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 51901), 2009 July-Sept (Box 2)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 51901), 2009 Oct-Dec (Box 2)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 51962), 2010 Apr-June (Box 1)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Sept (Box 1)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 51962), 2010 Oct-Dec (Box 1)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Agency Head meetings (Acc. 51901), 2009 (Box 2)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Disney (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Meeting with Secretary Gottshalk and David Smith (Acc. 51901), 2009 Aug 11 (Box 2)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Monthly reports (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Request to establish a regional office in the 19th District (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Sen. Hawkins (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Weekly reports (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-December (Box 5)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Weekly reports (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 5)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Weekly reports (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Commissioners: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 4)
  - Commissioners: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1991 July-Dec (Box 2)
  - Commissioners: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 January-June (Box 2)
  - Commissioners: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 4)
  - Commissioners: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 4)
  - Commissioners: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-December (Box 2)
  - Commissioners: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 2)
  - Commissioners: Strategic Planning S/C (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 4)
  - Commissioners: Strategic Planning subcommittee (Acc. 45144), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Commissioners: Strategic Planning S/C (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 4)
  - Commissioners: VHDA/DHCD Coordination (Acc. 44847), 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth, Secretary of the: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Commonwealth, Secretary of the: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Commonwealth, Secretary of the: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Commonwealth, Secretary of the: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Communications Division: Annual Report (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 1)
  - Communications Division: Communications Audit (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 1)
  - Communications Division: Community Affairs (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 1)
  - Communications Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 3)
  - Communications Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-December (Box 1)
  - Communications Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 1)
  - Communications Division: Government Affairs (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 1)
  - Communications Division: Minority Affairs (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 3)
  - Communications Division: Nonprofit Affairs (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 3)
  - Communications Division: Nonprofit Affairs (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 1)
  - Communications Division: Women and Housing Conference (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 3)
  - Community Reinvestment Act (CRA) (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 5)
  - Comprehensive Housing Affordability Strategy (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 8)
  - Council of State Housing Agencies Board meeting (Acc. 45238), 1984 January (Box 1)
  - Council of State Housing Agencies Board meeting (Acc. 45238), 1984 April (Box 1)
  - Deputy Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 January-June (Box 3)
  - Deputy Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 4)
  - Deputy Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 4)
  - Deputy Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-December (Box 3)
  - Deputy Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 3)
  - Director of Equity Investor Relations (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Director of Equity (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 4)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Agency Head meetings (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 6)
  - Economic Development - Agency retreat (Acc. 45238), 1988 (Box 2)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Agency Head retreats (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 6)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 July-December (Box 7)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 7)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-April (Box 7)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 May-August (Box 7)
  - Administration, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1991-1992 (Box 7)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 April-June (Box 6)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 July-September (Box 6)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: General Dynamics (Acc. 45144), 1991 (Box 6)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Strategic Planning (Acc. 44847), 1990 September (Box 8)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Strategic Planning (Acc. 45238), 1991 (Box 7)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Meeting with Secretary Framme (Acc. 44847), 1990 January (Box 8)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Meeting with Secretary Framme (Acc. 44847), 1990 April (Box 8)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Mid Year Assessment (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 8)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Public Information Office (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 6)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Weekly Reports (Acc. 45144), 1991 July-1992 June (Box 6)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Weekly Reports (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 7)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Weekly Reports (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 7)
  - Education, Secretary of: Commonwealth Education Strategy (Acc. 45268), 1993-1994 (Box 5)
  - Education, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Education, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Education, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 6)
  - Education, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Education, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 April-June (Box 6)
  - Education, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1993 October-December (Box 5)
  - Education, Secretary of: Long-term Strategic Plan (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 5)
  - EIS (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 3)
  - EIS Mission/Vision Strategic Planning Workshop (Acc. 45268), 1993 Dec (Box 3)
  - Employer Assisted Housing (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 5)
  - Ethyl (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Ethyl Advisory Committee (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Ethyl Property Discussions (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Articles of interest (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Articles of interest (Acc. 45144), 1991 (Box 2)
  - Executive Director: Articles of Interest (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Articles of Interest (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Budget (Acc. 44847), 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Budget (Acc. 45144), 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Executive Director: Budget (Acc. 45238), 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence - John Ritchie (Acc. 43861), 1977-1979 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence - John Ritchie (Acc. 43861), 1978-1979 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence - John Ritchie (Acc. 43861), 1979 Feb-Mar (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence - John Ritchie (Acc. 43861), 1979 May-July (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence - John Ritchie (Acc. 43861), 1979 Aug-Oct (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence - John Ritchie (Acc. 43861), 1979 Nov-Dec (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1991 July-Dec (Box 2)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 January-June (Box 2)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 April-June (Box 2)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-September (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1992 October-December (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-March (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 April-June (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-September (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1993 October-December (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-February (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence(Acc. 45268), 1994 March=April (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 May-June (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-Mar (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence (Acc. 51962), 2010 Oct-Dec (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: EIS (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Highlights of 1990 (Acc. 45144), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Executive Director: Highlights of 1993 (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Karl Bren (Acc. 44847), 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Meeting and speaking engagements, Miscellaneous (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 2)
  - Executive Director: Miscellaneous (Acc. 43861), 1977-1980 (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Miscellaneous (Acc. 43861), 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Resumes (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Resumes (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Resumes (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 2)
  - Fairfax Housing Summit (Acc. 45268), 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - Farmers Home Administration (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Farmers Home Administration (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Farmers Home Administration (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Farmers Home Administration (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Advisory Council: Affordable Housing (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 5)